<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Adam Kochan</title><link>https://www.adamkochan.com/</link><description>Recent content on Adam Kochan</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.adamkochan.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Melodrama' - Lorde Review</title><link>https://www.adamkochan.com/posts/melodrama-review/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.adamkochan.com/posts/melodrama-review/</guid><description>If you wanna go back to the January 2022 Hub click here.
&amp;ldquo;Man who thought Lorde was a 1-Hit wonder SHOCKED when the Whole Album Bops” Score: 8/10
Stand-Out Song: Green Light (Is this too Safe?)
Other Favs: Homemade Dynamite, The Lourve, Liability, Hard Feels, Supercut
Recomended if You Like: Carly Rae Jepsen, Bleachers, Literally any Jack Antonoff Produced Album Ever
Ok Lorde, I’m sorry that’s on me, here I was thinking you were a 1-hit wonder and I hated that hit (Royals is Overhyped, fite me), this album showed me I was completely wrong.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.adamkochan.com/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 08:50:21 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.adamkochan.com/about/</guid><description>hi there! i&amp;rsquo;m reno.</description></item><item><title>'Wide Awake!' - Parquet Courts Review</title><link>https://www.adamkochan.com/posts/wide-awake-review/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.adamkochan.com/posts/wide-awake-review/</guid><description>If you wanna go back to the January 2022 Hub click here.
“If you are looking to head bang to smart, political punk this is the album for you” Score: 7/10
Stand-Out Song: Almost Had to Start a Fight/In and Out of Paitience
Other Favs: Tenderness, FreeBird II, Before The Water Gets Too High, Wide Awake
Recomended if You Like: The Strokes, Franz Ferdinand, The Clash, &amp;ldquo;Harder&amp;rdquo; LCD Soundsystem
Well that was fun, This is like if you took LCD Soundsystem, added in some Franz Ferdinand, some Scott Pilgrim vs the World, and then gave them a Political Channel on Youtube.</description></item><item><title>January 2022 Album Reviews</title><link>https://www.adamkochan.com/posts/album-a-day-jan-2022-intro/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.adamkochan.com/posts/album-a-day-jan-2022-intro/</guid><description>Note: I&amp;rsquo;ll update these with the link to the review as they get listened to!
Injury Reserve - By the Time I Get to Phoenix Death Grips - The Money Store Sufjan Stevens - Carrie &amp;amp; Lowell LCD Soundsystem- This is Happening King Gizzard &amp;amp; The Lizard Wizard - Nonagon Infinity Bon Iver - 22, A Million Parquet Courts - Wide Awake! DJ Sabrina The Teenage DJ - Charmed Lorde - Melodrama The National - Sleep Well Beast The War on Drugs - Holding On George Clanton - Slide LOONA - Max &amp;amp; Match Roisin Murphy - Roisin Machine The Comet is Coming - Trust In The Lifeforce of the Deep Mystery Low - Quorum / Dancing and Blood / Fly Grizzly Bear - Shields Weezer - Weezer (The White Album) BTS - The Most Beautiful Moment in Life: Young Forever D&amp;rsquo;Angelo - Black Messiah tricot - Jodeki (上出来) BADBADNOTGOOD - Talk Memory Charli XCX - How I&amp;rsquo;m Feeling Now Gorillaz - Plastic Beach Todd Terje - It&amp;rsquo;s Album Time Fiona Apple - The Idler Wheel Is Wiser Than the Driver of the Screw and Whipping Cords Will Serve You More Than Ropes Will Ever Do Jeff Rosenstock - SKA Dream Run The Jewels - Run The Jewels 2</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.adamkochan.com/links/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.adamkochan.com/links/</guid><description>My email: me@renodubois.com
GitHub Sourcehut Twitter Twitch Mastodon</description></item></channel></rss>